smartwebchoices.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy - Scanguard

**Personal Information.** This Privacy Policy applies to the personal data of users that is collected or used by SS Protect Limited, doing business as Scanguard(“Scanguard”) as set forth more fully below (the “Personal Information”). You should also read our Terms and Conditions, Billing Terms and DMCA Policy which are incorporated herein by reference. When you use our Services, you are agreeing to our rules and policies regarding your data and you expressly consent to us collecting, processing and using and storing your Personal Information, as described below. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.** Scanguard may modify this Privacy Policy, from time to time to reflect changes in or requirements of the law or modifications or updates to the Services made in accordance with our Terms and Conditions. Scanguard will notify you if such change materially affects your rights under this Privacy Policy. Changes will not apply retrospectively and, unless the change is required immediately for legal reasons, notice of the modified terms will be provided a reasonable period prior to the changes taking effect. If you do not accept and agree to this Privacy Policy, then you must not access or use the Services.

### What Personal Information Do We Collect

**Information you give us.** When you sign up for a Scanguard account, we keep the basic account information you give us, like your name, email address, telephone number, password and payment information. We also collect and store your Personal Information as you use the Services and each time you interact with Scanguard, for example, when you update information in your control panel, communicate with us by telephone or email, order or download new Services, register a licence or change your device and complete forms on our website. We also store information about the Services you purchase, such as the activation code, date of purchase, and information relating to any support issue. 

**Automatic Information.** We may collect information about the device you access the Services from, such as the IP address or other unique device identifiers. If you access your Scanguard account from a mobile device, that mobile device may also provide us with details of your location. Most mobile devices allow you to disable this functionality. Scanguard uses "cookies" and other technologies to collect data that enable us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our website. Cookies are files sent to your browser and stored on your computer. Scanguard uses cookies to gather general information about your visits to our website, the files you have designated for backup, the configuration of your computer and your computer’s interaction with the Services, and stores this information in log files. Scanguard uses this information to understand traffic and downloads on our website, enabling us to improve the website, provide the best online experience possible, and improve our customer service. 

### We use the following types of cookies on our site:

**Strictly necessary cookies** \- These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website and remembering which files you have marked for backup. Without these cookies, services you have asked for, like security or e-billing, cannot be provided.

**Performance cookies** \- These cookies collect information about how you use the website. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies you and are only used to improve how the website works.

**Functionality cookies** \- These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make, such as the configuration of your computer, to provide enhanced, more personal features.

**Advertising cookies** \- These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are placed on the website by advertisers and advertising networks, with our permission. They remember that you have visited the site and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Scanguard uses analytics data and the DoubleClick cookies for advertising purposes. You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) Google has additional information available about their Policy for [Advertising based on Interests and Location](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/143465?hl=en-GB). 

**Other Technologies** \- We may also use other Internet technologies, such as web beacons or pixel tags and other similar technologies, to deliver or communicate with cookies and analyze your use of the Services. We also may include web beacons in e-mail messages so that we know when you have opened an email message received from Scanguard.

You may disable cookies by changing the settings on your browser. Check the help menu in your browser for further information. Remember that if you disable cookies it is likely to affect how our website works and you may not be able to access or use certain areas of our website or functionality. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will place cookies when you log on to our website.

**Personal Information regarding children.** The Services are not intended for use by individuals who cannot enter a legally binding a contract. Accordingly, Scanguard does not intentionally gather any Personal Information about individuals who are under the age of eighteen (18). If you are under eighteen (18) years of age or otherwise lack the capacity to enter into a binding contract do not use our Services. If Scanguard becomes aware that it has collected Personal Information from someone under the age of majority, such information will be deleted immediately. 

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We use your Personal Information to provide you with the Services, administer your Scanguard account, send you information about the Services (including updates and modifications), process payments, generate and review reports and data about our user base and Service usage patterns, analyze the accuracy, effectiveness, usability, or popularity of the Services, improve the content and features of the Services and allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you see on the Services. In order to do so, we may use your Personal Information to contact you through desktop alerts, SMS/Text messaging, email and live chat.

If you wish to change the way we use your data, see your options below. Please be aware that if you choose not to provide us with certain Personal Information, we may not be able to make Services available to you.

### How We Disclose Your Personal Information

We don’t sell or share any Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. We may share your information in the following circumstances:

**Third Party Service Providers.** We engage third parties to perform certain functions on our behalf. They will have access to your data to the extent needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. We require all third parties to process your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by applicable data protection laws.

**Partners and Sponsors.** Some of the Services are offered or promoted to our customers in conjunction with a partner or sponsor, or another brand or company within Just Develop It Limited corporate family. To the extent permitted by applicable law, sometimes we might share your information with other third parties with a view to offering you other products and services that we think you may find to be of interest. If you do not wish to receive such offers, please use the unsubscribe link on the email communication you receive or contact us at [support@scanguard.com](mailto:support@scanguard.com).

**Sale of Business.** If Scanguard is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a material portion of its assets, change in corporate control, or insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings, you will be notified via email or a prominent notice will be placed on the website of any such change in ownership or use of your Personal Information as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Information.

**Compliance with Laws and Policies.** Scanguard reserves the right to disclose your Personal Information to third parties if we believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with a law, regulation, or governmental or judicial warrant, rule, order or subpoena; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Scanguard; or (3) enforce the Scanguard Terms and Conditions, including this Privacy Policy. 

### How We Communicate with You

Scanguard may, from time to time, send you emails, desktop alerts or other communications, including: (1) notifications of detected problems with your Service; (2) notifications concerning the expiration of your account; (3) activity status reports; (4) service and software upgrade notices; (5) notices concerning new or related Services from Scanguard (or other service providers as discussed in this Privacy Policy); (6) notices concerning enhancements to the Services; (7) price change notices for the Services; (8) notifications regarding suspected unlawful or inappropriate use; and (9) requests for feedback on the Services.

If you wish to change the types of communications you receive from us or opt out of receiving any future communications, you can do so. See Your Options below.

### How We Protect Your Data

**General.** Scanguard has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your data. Personal Information provided to Scanguard is stored in secure facilities with access restricted to authorized personnel only. Although we make good faith efforts to store the Personal Information we collect in a secure operating environment that is not accessible to unauthorized users, we cannot guarantee complete security. 

**Secure Payments.** To provide secure credit card processing when ordering from us, orders placed on our website are processed through a payment gateway which operates under its own privacy policy. If you choose to purchase or license the Services online using a credit card, the credit card information is sent to Scanguard using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption, an industry-standard method for protecting data as it travels over the Internet, or a similar encryption technology that may become accepted as an industry standard, or better encryption method, in the future. To learn more about our credit card processing vendors and their respective privacy and other policies which apply when you make a payment through their services, please review the terms of their own privacy policies 

### Your Options

**Email Communications.** If you wish to change the types of communications you receive from us or opt out of receiving any future communications, you may do so by modifying your profile on your control panel, by emailing your request to us at [support@scanguard.com](mailto:support@scanguard.com), or by clicking on the appropriate link in any Scanguard email communication that you receive.

**Correcting Your Personal Information.** You can access the Personal Information that we collect via your control panel. You can correct factual errors in your Personal Information on your control panel or by sending a request to [support@scanguard.com](mailto:support@scanguard.com). Please provide sufficient details regarding the error. To protect your privacy and security, we take commercially reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making any corrections to your Personal Information.

### Your EU Data Protection Rights

**Location of Personal Information and Transfers.** Scanguard processes Personal Information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your Personal Information on a server located outside the country where you live. By using the Services, you freely and specifically give Scanguard your consent to export your Personal Information outside of the EEA, including to the US and understand that data stored outside of the EEA may be subject to lawful requests by the courts or law enforcement authorities in the countries in which it is stored.

**Access Requests.** You have the right to request a copy of the Personal Information we hold about you. Scanguard will take commercially reasonable steps to provide you with such access and to correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete.

### Third Party Links and Services

Scanguard may provide links to other third party websites as a convenience to you (collectively, the “Third Party Websites”). Please exercise care when visiting any Third Party Websites. The Third Party Websites have separate and independent privacy policies, notices and terms of use which govern your use of such websites and their use of any information they collect, we recommend you read these policies carefully. Scanguard disclaims all liability for Personal Information you provide to any Third Party Websites.

### Dispute Resolution

Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of Personal Information should be directed to Scanguard at the address given below. Scanguard will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personal Information in accordance with the principles contained in this Privacy Policy.

If Scanguard is unable to resolve your complaint, you can escalate the issue in accordance with the dispute resolution procedure set out in the Terms and Conditions.

### Scanguard Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments, please contact us at [support@scanguard.com](mailto:support@scanguard.com) or at the address listed below: 

SS Protect Limited,  
Larch House,  
Parklands Business Park,  
Denmead,  
Hampshire,  
PO7 6XP,  
United Kingdom
